Amit Macwan

Admin Coordinator



Contact

Address:

C/22, Sudarshan Apts., Nr. Saibaba Mandir, Sattadhar Cross Rd., Ghatlodia, Ahmedabad-380061.

Phone:

+91 95740 00807

Email:

macwanamit01@gmail.com

LinkedIn:

linkedin.com/macwanamit01

Languages

English Hindi Gujarati

Hobbies

- Listening Music
- Long Drive
- Traveling

Summary

Highly 17+ years of experienced and compassionate facility coordinator with a passion for healthcare. Proven track record in managing the clinical and administrative operations house-keeping, security, transport, event coordination, stock inventory, pest control, water sanitation, bio-medical waste management and patient care attendant.

Experience

Hospital Administrator – 12/01/2023 to present

(Sakalchand Patel University)-

Nootan General Hospital, Medical College & Research Center

- Responsible for Housekeeping Management
- Security Management
- Biomedical waste Management
- Pest Control Management
- Vender Management
- Oxygen Plant Management
- Generator Management
- Responsible for New policy and other changes of employees
- Monitoring work schedules for all employs (3rd and 4th class)
- Ensure patient medical records to be kept up to date
- Monitoring expenses of facility management

Admin Coordinator - 02/2021 to 09/2022

Blue Diamond Facility Management Services LLC, Dubai-UAE

- Manage day-to-day facilities and operations for Mazaya Site, Dubai-Al Ain Road.
- Handling 40 resources across the site.
- Responsible for Monthly MIS, Snag Report, Preparing Quotations, Incident Reports, PPM Reports.
- Physically visit for Snag update and verification to the concern location.
- Generating SO for monthly invoice process.
- Preparing quotation list as well as LPO list.
- Preparing Minutes of Meeting report and coordinate with concern person.

Admin Manager - 01/2019 to 11/2020

SMS Hospital & Medical Institute, Ahmedabad-Gujarat (IND)

- Handling Facility operations (House-keeping, Patient care Attendant, Security, Transport, Billing, Event Coordination, Stock Inventory, Pest Control, Garden Management, Biomedical Waste Management) in the hospital as well as Medical College.
- Responsible for any issues on floor.

- Follow UP the billing process for the concern vendors.
- Follow-up with the supervisors as well as facility manager of outsource agency.

Asst. Officer – Facility - 10/2013 to 01/2019 **GCS Medical College, Hospital & Research Center,** Ahmedabad-Gujarat (IND)

I have been awarded A Certificate of Appreciation of 'NABH EXHIBITION Quality for Mass'.

- Follow up the billing process for the concern vendors.
- Follow-up with supervisors as well as facility manager of outsource Agency.
- Software operation in Facility Department.
- MIS reporting.

Customer Care Executive - 07/2009 to 05/2013

Sterling Hospital, Rajkot-Gujarat (IND)

- Worked as OPD In-charge in Front Office Department.
- Attend and answer all the enquiries of patient politely & promptly.
- Follow up consultant's instruction for patients.
- Maintain all the records and register accordingly.
- Responsible for Linen, Housekeeping, Transport, Hostel Management.

Administrator - 07/2007 to 07/2009

SAVA Hospital, Surendranagar-Gujarat (IND)

- Scheduling of consultant's OPD.
- Accommodation arrangement for nursing staff in hostel management.
- Front office In-charge.
- Management of Medical equipment & instruments.
- Housekeeping & other staff Management.

•

Public Relation Office - 07/2005 to 06/2007 Sterling Hospital, Ahmedabad-Gujarat (IND)

- Patient enquiry handling.
- Patient admission process.
- In-Patient query management.
- Discharge Process.

Skill Highlights

Strong organizational skills attention to detail.

- Ability to proficiently use Microsoft Word, Excel and Email.
- Ability to proficiently use computer and standard office equipment.
- Ability to resolve associate issues effectively and efficiently.

QUALIFICATION

Bachelor of Arts: Gujarat University - 1999
Gujarat University, Ahmedabad.

Certifications

PGDHHM Hospital Management (certificate): Symbiosis
International University, Pune – 2011-2012

Personal Details

Date of Birth: 30th October 1976

Gender : Male **Nationality :** Indian